原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     千只鹤飞过波千鸟  tong大梨
翻译     VioletCheng  AlgerDestiny  不见彩虹屁
校对     屯栗子
时间轴     兜兜兜爹
后期     渔夫
总监     屯栗子
辛普森一家
第三十一季  第九集
弗兰德斯一家
现在归迪士尼了
没事做的手是恶魔的工具
给灵魂的白面包
流浪汉食品供应站
没沙发了孩子们  我送给穷人了
No couch, boys. I gave it to the poor.
内德  内德
Neddy? Neddy.
茉德  你回来了
Oh, Maude, you've come back.
穿的整整齐齐  还摸不着
Completely clothed and untouchable.
这是我做过的最性感的梦
This is the sexiest dream I've ever had.
等等  茉德
Wait, Maudie.
啵一个嘛
Just one little kiss.
只亲舌头不沾嘴唇
All tongue, no lips.
跟茉德一样
Just like Maude.
粑粑  你哭啥
Daddy, why are you crying?
给胡子浇浇水而已
Oh, just watering the old lip lawn.
我做了一个关于你妈妈的梦
I had a dream about your mom.
你梦见过她吗
Don't you ever dream about her?
快点  麻麻  快点
Faster, Mommy, faster.
怎么了  托德
What's wrong, Todd?
我再也忘不了了
I can never unsee that.
没事的儿子  噩梦而已
It's okay, son. Just a bad dream.
想喝点温开水吗
Want some lukewarm water?
爸爸  我记不得妈妈长什么样了
Daddy, I can't remember what Mommy looks like.
我想我有一两段你妈妈的视频
I think I might have a video or two of your mother.
怎么了
What's wrong?
我在按妈妈的美容旧法敷面膜
I'm doing Mommy's old skin routine.
这是个悲伤的好办法
Now, that's the healthy way to grieve.
跟茉德  罗德  托德过圣诞
跟内德过新年
耶稣宝宝  耶稣少年  耶稣本人
我怕怕
I'm scared.
我对你有信心
Well, I have faith in you.
你们是谁
Who are you people,
你们对我家人做了什么
and what have you done with my family?
回答我
Answer me!
老爹  我们每次叫你给车道铲雪
Oh, Dad, every time we make you shovel the driveway,
你总能去什么可怕的地方
you wind up someplace crazy.
跟我们一起吃晚饭吧
Won't you join us for dinner?
他肯定来
He sure will.
我明天来接他
I'll pick him up tomorrow.
麻麻人这么好
Mommy was so nice.
她现在还是一样好  罗德托德
And she still is, Roddily Doddily.
你怎么知道  你有她消息吗
How do you know? Have you heard from her?
没有
Oh, uh, n-no, sir.
但是信仰就是无凭无据地去相信
But, uh, faith is believing in something without proof.
你看不见我胡子下面的嘴唇
Uh, you can't see my lip below my mustache,
但你知道它在那儿
but you know it's there.
-我能看看吗  -不能
- Can I see it? - No.
我数学老师说
My math teacher said
无凭无据地相信是很疯狂的
believing in something without proof is crazy.
你觉得约瑟夫的彩衣是疯狂的
You think the coat of many colors was crazy?
诺亚方舟和圣灵是疯狂的
Noah's ark and the Holy Ghost, crazy?
别跟我说你在质疑先知巴兰
Don't tell me you're doubting Balaam's talking ass.
麻麻  如果你还记得我  给我点暗示
Mommy, if you still remember me, give me a sign.
我是侯默·辛普森
This is Homer Simpson auditioning
我正在参选世界空气吉他锦标赛
for the air guitar championship of the world.
我要打败你  比昂·特拉克
I'm taking you down, Bjorn Turoque.
春田第一教堂
上帝无处不在
但他要你
一周一次必须出现在这儿
*赞美上帝*
*Praise God from whom*
*万事如意*
*All blessings flow*
*赞美上帝*
*Praise God*
*是时候离开*
*It's almost time to go*
*这无聊的布道*
*This boring sermon*
*得马上停止*
*Must end soon*
*竞技场足球赛*
*Arena football's*
*正午开球*
*On at noon*
献给垃圾球迷的垃圾足球赛
就为那一个简单的理由  我们是对的
And for that simple reason, we are right
主教派是错错错的
and Episcopalians are wrong, wrong, wrong.
现在我得有请
Now I'd like to invite
我们教区最小的教徒上前来
our littlest parishioners to the front.
葛蒂  来点旅行音乐吧
Gertie, a little traveling music, please?
我们会尽快把她换成斯波蒂菲
Soon as we can, we're replacing her with Spotify.
我要吃掉中央C键
I'm taking middle C.
祝福小小我街道
告诉我  年幼的基督徒们
So, tell me, young Christians,
如果你可以跟耶稣宝宝对话
if you could speak to Baby Jesus,
你会说什么
what would you say?
我会说谢谢你出生
I'd say thank you for being born,
给我们带来了圣诞节
'cause that gave us Christmas.
萌死了
Mmm, I'm killing it.
拉尔夫  你会说什么
Ralph, what would you say?
我会说  "耶稣宝宝
I'd say, "Baby Jesus,
谢谢你为我们的罪恶死去"
thank you for dying for our shins."
你呢托德  你会说什么
And you, Todd? What would you say?
我哭到失声了
I lost my voice from crying.
小伙子振作起来
Oh, come on, young man.
你离我更近
You're my closer.
你会对耶稣说什么
What would you say to Jesus?
我会说
I'd say...
感谢你什么都没做
thanks for nothing!
我妈妈死了  永远都回不来了
My mommy's dead and she's never coming back,
我再也不相信上帝了
and I don't believe in God anymore.
不  不
No. No!
谢天谢地这些收集篮是空的
Thank God these collection baskets were empty.
不用谢
You're welcome.
*我们的小托德出了大问题*
*A mighty problem is our Todd*
*他对上帝的信仰*
*His faith in God*
*正在瓦解*
*Is failing*
*侯默意外地害死了他的妈妈*
*Homer accidentally killed his mom*
*他把她撞下篱笆*
*He knocked her off a railing*
儿子  我来温柔地跟你说一下
Now, son, let me put this gently.
我们都要下地狱了
We're all going to hell!
你在上帝自己的房子里打开了质疑的大门
You opened a doorway to disbelief in God's own house!
上帝为什么需要这么多房子
Why does God need so many houses?
不能捐一些给穷人吗
Couldn't some go to poor people?
你给我打住  小子
You just stop right there, boy.
不许你质疑
You do not question
上帝持有的不动产和免税状况
God's real estate holdings and tax-free status.
我要去撒撒气
I have to let off a little steam.
呸  呸  呸
Shucks! Shucks! Shucks!
说脏话罐
冲动想法罐
裤子抽太紧罐
乱糟糟的胡子罐
好了  年轻人  我要去和教父视频了
That's it. Young man, I am FaceTiming the reverend.
牧师手机
牧师家
牧师湖边小屋
牧师办公室
牧师姐姐家
牧师训练室
牧师兼泌尿科医生
勒弗乔伊神父
神父
Reverend,
我知道你讨厌我打扰你
I know you hate it when I bother you.
没事的  没事的
It's okay. It's okay.
我在我女儿的芭蕾表演会上
I'm at my daughter's ballet recital.
她表现得好吗
Oh, is she good?
讲真的  他们有一个是好的吗
Seriously, are any of them good?
神父  就像红海里的法老军队一样
Reverend, like the pharaoh's army in the Red Sea,
法老军队在追捕以色列人过程中被红海淹没
我不知道该怎么办了
I'm in over my head.
我的异教徒儿子现在就需要你
My heathen son needs you right now.
抱歉  我得挂了
Oh, sorry, got to go.
我要去为芭蕾舞演出
I have to read the last rites...
做最后的祈祷
for the art of ballet.
主  请彻底地惩罚我的儿子吧
Lord, please punish my boy thoroughly
也许他就会再次相信你神圣的仁慈之心
so he may once again believe in thine divine mercy.
-爸爸  我有个问题  -你也有问题吗
- Daddy, I have a problem. - Oh, you, too?
我不小心看了《我为喜剧狂》
I accidentally watched a 30 Rock by mistake.
我的好孩子啊
Oh! Oh, my good, good boy.
所以可以看吗
So it's okay to watch?
只能看肯尼斯  只能看肯尼斯
Just Kenneth. Just Kenneth.
早上好  罗德  托德  上帝
Good morning, Rod. Todd. God.
-早上好  -早
- Good morning. - Morning.
我们依旧继续我们的日常
Let us, uh, stiffly resume our nice, regular routine.
亲爱的主  感谢你提供这顿早饭
Dear Lord, we thank you for this breakfast,
每个平平无奇的谷物圈都代表着上帝无限的爱
each generic brand Circle-O a symbol of God's unending love.
-阿门  -阿门
- Amen. - Amen.
托德
Todd?
儿子  能说句阿门吗
Son? Can I just get an amen?
没有阿门的祈祷
A prayer without an amen
就像杜丝先生棒棒糖没有夹心
is like a Tootsie Pop without a center.
我要为想到了"杜丝先生"这个词道歉
Oh, I apologize for thinking the word "Tootsie."
但是一定有方法
But there must be a way
能吓得我儿子重拾信仰
to scare religion back into my son.
有什么人间地狱能让他去体验一下吗
Isn't there some hell on earth I could briefly place him in?
让我进去  儿子
Let me in, boy!
校车随时都会到了
The school bus will be here any minute!
想要找到你的衣服  只需要解决以下谜题
To find your clothes, just solve this series of clues:
什么东西会叫[树皮]但是不咬人
what has bark but no bite?
狗吗
Um, the dog?
错  是树
Wrong. A tree.
再来一个  如果飞机坠毁在
Here's another. If a plane crashes
达科塔的南北边境处
on the border of North and South Dakota,
你要把幸存者埋在哪
where do you bury the survivors?
明尼苏达州
Uh, Minnesota.
错
Wrong.
你不用埋葬幸存者  他们是幸存者
You don't bury the survivors. They're survivors!
我不理解  但是我要埋了你
I don't understand, but I'll bury you.
这么说吧  如果你能答对最后一个
Tell you what. I'll give you your pants back
我就把裤子还给你
if you can answer this last one.
-什么东西头顶有两根头发  -嗯
- What has two hairs on top... - Right.
-是某人的爸爸  -某人的爸爸  好
- is somebody's dad... - Somebody's dad, yes.
从现在开始他非常生气了
and starting right now he's getting quite mad?
我不知道  但是快把裤子给我  小子
I don't know, but just give me my pants, boy!
我能拍照吗
Can we take pictures?
等等  你也看见了吗
Wait, you see that, too?
辛普森家
That Simpson house
会让他敬畏上帝
will put the fear of God in him.
把你的裤子给我
Give me your pants.
托德·傅兰德  我驱逐你离开家
Todd Flanders, I cast thee out.
*他小小的头脑*
*His little mind*
*充满了大大的疑惑*
*Is filled with doubt*
*所以我们需要驱逐他离开家门*
*So now we have to cast him out*
*你会知道主和蔼可亲*
*You'll learn the Lord is sweet*
*在他十二米的旅途中*
*On his journey of 40 feet*
引文
必须剪草坪
管好你家孩子
引文
必须采用引文
爸爸  你现在更爱我了吗
Daddy, do you love me more now?
你这么问
Just by asking,
就犯下了骄傲的原罪
you have committed the sin of pride.
好的  内德  好的
Yes, Ned, yes.
他可以在我们家住到明天
We'll keep him here till tomorrow.
好  我会给他讲睡前故事的
Yes, I'll read him a good bedtime story.
对  对  不能有巫师
Right, right. No wizards.
不能有异教徒  不能有异端思想
No pagans. No wild things.
要不给他读《饥饿的毛毛虫》吧
How about The Very Hungry Caterpillar?
儿童图画书  讲述毛毛虫的一生
不行  那书宣扬了暴食
No, that celebrates gluttony.
那《大红狗克里弗》呢
Clifford the Big Red Dog?
畅销儿童读物系列  讲述巨型犬克里弗的故事
我看是《恶魔狗克里弗》吧
Clifford the satanic abomination.
那《大家来噗噗》呢
Everyone Poops?
日本儿童读物  科普人类的排便习惯
我看不行[我就不噗噗]
Not me.
托德  托德
Todd. Psst! Todd.
我知道抛下家庭的信仰是什么感觉
I know what it's like to leave the faith of your family.
太谢谢你了  丽莎
Thank you so much, Lisa.
终于有人懂我了
At last, someone gets it.
不过我为你找了一位神
But have I got a god for you.
考虑一下佛祖吧  他给人带来内心的平静
Consider the Buddha. He brings peace from within.
他避免自我意识的缺陷
He avoids the pitfalls of ego,
他爱做瑜伽  还喜欢尤达
he loves yoga and Yoda,
《星球大战》系列中德高望重的绝地大师
他还减了肥
and he's lost weight.
那你死后会发生什么
What happens when you die?
你会转世化身为人或动物或鬼魂
You get reincarnated as a human or an animal or a ghost.
佛祖才不是神  上帝也不是神
Pass. Buddha's no god, and neither is God.
别担心  我会搞定他的
Don't worry, I'll get him.
对了  你把大卫·鲍威转世成什么了
By the way, what did you reincarnate David Bowie as?
英国摇滚歌手  2016年去世
救救我  亲爱的  我是鲍威
Help me, love. It's Bowie.
我最近冥想太多了
I've been meditating too much.
托德在哪里
Where's Todd?
太可怕了
It was horrible.
我醒来时他已经把我房间打扫干净了
I woke up, and he'd cleaned my room.
什么样的疯子会做这种事
What kind of psycho does that?
你好呀  辛普森爷爷
Hi, Grampa Simpson.
你在直接跟我说话吗
You're talking to me directly?
我的Alexa都不会这么做
Even my Alexa won't do that.
亚马逊公司推出的人工智能助理
和他一起生活真是累死人
Being with him has made me so tired.
《华氏451度》
反乌托邦科幻小说
马姬
Hey, Marge,
你可能已经注意到了
you may have noticed
我前几天洗了个澡
I took a shower earlier this week.
不行  不行
I can't. I can't.
托德在我们家的时候不行
Not with Todd in the house.
孩子们在家里已经有十年了
Oh, we've had kids in the house for ten years.
不是这个意思  他已经习惯安静了
Not that one. He's used to silence.
-他会听见我们的  -不会的
- He'll hear us. - No, he won't.
我听得见
Yes, I will!
我们得把那孩子弄走
Oof! Got to get rid of that kid.
这可能吗
Can it be?
我的老天
Oh, my goodness!
我们救世主的脸在一片普通的面包上
The face of our Lord and Savior in a humble piece of toast?
很显然  没人能做到这个
Clearly, no human could have made this.
不是吗
Huh?
主说
And the Lord said,
"吃了它  因为我是镇上的吐司"
"Take this and eat, for I am the toast of the town."
也指受人尊敬喜爱的人
-是你画上去的  -不  不
- You drew that on. - No, no.
是上帝画上去的  他还签了名
God drew it on. Look, he signed it.
"椰稣"  看到了吗
"Jebus." See?
为什么上帝要把耶稣弄到吐司上
Why would God make toast that looked like Jesus?
因为父母总是炫耀孩子们的照片
'Cause parents are always showing off pictures of their kids?
落选的吐司
这么多无辜的面包因为我的罪过而丧命
So much innocent bread died for my sins.
太无辜了
So innocent.
*什么是善*
*What is good*
*什么是罪过*
*And what is sin*
*巴仔想要摆脱他*
*Bart wants to get rid of him*
这是托德
Yo, this is Todd.
我得和他住一间房  直到他重拾信仰
I have to share my room until he believes in God again.
你不信上帝吗  这太疯狂了
You don't believe in God? Well, that's crazy.
除了那博爱  万能的存在  谁还能创造出
Who else but an all-loving, omnipotent being
如此美好的扒裤子和拧乳头活动呢
could create beautiful wedgies and purple nurples?
别这么快下结论
Not so fast.
万一我才是宇宙中唯一的存在
What if I'm the only being in the universe,
而你们都只是我的心理投射呢
and you're all my mental projections?
投射这个吧
Project this!
我肯定很希望这事发生
I must have wanted this to happen!
既然你知道坏孩子是怎么形成的了
So now that you see how bad kids turn out,
你想回家了  对吗
you want to go home, right?
别再把我们当反例了
Stop using us as examples!
我觉得你的朋友们都会下地狱
I believe your friends are all going to Hell.
-没错  -太棒了
- Yeah! - Cool!
我听见你们了
I hear you!
为什么那个小笨蛋听到了
What doesn't that little twerp hear?
我不知道  但是我听到了
I don't know, but I heard that.
好了  他现在听不到我们了
Okay. He can't hear us now.
我能啊
Yes, I can.
你正在解开自己的衬衫  辛普森先生
You're unbuttoning your shirt, Mr. Simpson.
这小孩必须走
纸上写的是什么
What does that paper say?
你好  托德
Oh. Hi, Todd.
还在寻找开悟吗
Still seeking enlightenment?
我跟你说了  现在不行
I told you, not now.
也许当我变成一只蠕虫回来的时候
Maybe I'll reconsider your stupid beliefs
会考虑一下你那愚蠢的信仰
when I come back as a worm.
在佛教里  这意味着你快要接受了
In Buddhism, that's halfway to "Yes"!
听着  托德  你没必要去信这个
Look, Todd, you don't have to believe.
在教堂里只要微笑点头  还可以打瞌睡
In church, just smile and nod, but be sleeping on the inside.
这在工作中也有效
That works at work, too.
但是我真的不相信
But I really don't believe.
我妈妈去世之后再也不回来让我很难过
I'm sad because my mommy's gone and never coming back.
你知道心里是什么滋味吗
You know how that feels?
我理解
Oh, do I.
不  不要再经历一遍了  不要
Oh, no, don't relive it. Don't!
你晚上10点都没回家吃晚饭
You don't come home for dinner till 10:00 at night.
你从来做不出任何值得吃的东西
You never cook anything worth eating.
谁想为一个失败者做饭呢
Well, who wants to cook for a failure?
天呐  女人  为什么你会嫁给我
Good God, woman, why did you marry me?
为了惹我妈生气  而且还见效了
To piss off my mother, and it worked!
告诉孩子我很爱他  但是我不善于告别
Tell the kid I love him, but I'm as bad at goodbyes
就像我不擅长选丈夫一样
as I am at picking husbands.
我妈妈离家出走了
My mom is gone.
我的冰激凌也不见了
And so is my ice cream.
我的头发也没了
And so is my hair!
老谋子  我要一醉方休  快点
Moe, I got to get drunk. And fast.
没妈的孩子
我也来一杯
I'll take one, too.
怎么
What the...?!
我一无所有  给我一杯酒
I'm losing everything. Just give me a drink!
抱歉  弗兰德斯  我不能给你倒酒
I'm sorry, Flanders. I can't pour you a drink.
你人太好了  只是我爱莫能助
You're too good. It's just, it's not something I can do.
我求求你了
Please. I'm begging you.
好了  二十四美元
Yeah, that's $24.
*内德·弗兰德斯今天喝酒了*
*Ned Flanders is drinking today*
*哈利路亚*
*Allelujah*
*他的儿子误入歧途*
*His son Todd has gone astray*
*哈利路亚*
*Allelujah*
*举起你的酒杯一饮而尽*
*Raise your mug and drink it down*
*哈利路亚*
*Allelujah*
小费
*在这座小镇最差的酒吧*
*In the worst bar in this town*
*哈利路亚*
*Allelujah*
侯默  我一直认为
You know, Homer, I always thought
你证明了上帝是存在的
you proved the existence of God.
你从悬崖上摔下来  但是人没事
I mean, you fall off cliffs, and you're fit as a fiddle.
那不是吹牛吗
Well, ain't that a diddle!
这就是
So this is what it's like
看不起别人的感觉
to look down on someone.
你知道吗  内德  也许
You know what, Ned? There may...
也许天堂不存在
there may not be a heaven,
但是和你一起喝醉感觉不是很糟
but getting drunk with you ain't hell.
你太好了
Oh, you're great.
这是一个很棒的开始
This is the beginning of a beautiful...
你撞死了他们
You killed them!
你是我遇到过最差的优步司机
This is the worst Uber ride ever!
我要给你四星了
You're getting four stars.
不
No...!
天堂
欢迎内德
侯默也能来吗
欢迎来到天堂
Welcome to Heaven.
上帝  这和我想象中的一样美丽
Oh, Lord. It's just as beautiful as I pictured it.
这是你的想象  内德
This is your version, Ned.
侯默也有他的想象
Homer gets his, too.
我不觉得自己投入了很大的精力
So, not like I'm feeling I put in way too much work,
侯默也参与进来了吗
but Homer got in, too?
几年以前  懒惰成为了一种美德
Well, a couple of years ago, sloth became a virtue.
我不太明白
I don't really understand it.
你必须和我孩子谈谈
You'd have to talk to my kid.
他三十三岁还宅在家里
He's 33 and still lives at home.
我经历了一些事情  好吗
I've been through some stuff, man.
亚伯拉罕·林肯
Abe Lincoln!
你知道斯皮尔伯格
Did you know the picture
那部关于我生平的电影是最卖座的吗
about my life is Spielberg's biggest movie?
不  那《大白鲨》和《侏罗纪公园》系列
No! What about Jaws and E.T., and all the Jurassic...?
我在颁奖礼上表现如何
Well, how did I do in the awards?
-你打败了《逃离德黑兰》  -什么
- You were beaten by Argo. - Argo?!
那是我在影院里看过最糟糕的一部电影
That was the worst experience I ever had in a theater.
你们还有其他人要见
You have other people to see.
-带上通行证  -我们是访客
- Wear these passes. - Visitors?
真奇怪
Hmm, that's odd.
这一定说明你们的躯体还未死去
It must mean that your bodies aren't dead yet.
*我们需要你  上帝在上*
*We need you now oh God on high*
*别让愚蠢的弗兰德斯和侯默逝去*
*So stupid Flanders and Homer don't die*
内德·弗兰德斯  我向你保证我会倾尽所能
Ned Flanders, I swear to you I will use every ounce of skill
让你起死回生
in my body to bring you back to life.
那侯默怎么办
What about Homer?
顺其自然吧
Mm, que será, será.
天呐  他们在聚众祈祷
Oh, my. They're holding a vigil.
看爸爸一生曾经影响过多少人
Look how many, many lives Dad touched.
那是弗兰德斯的祈祷团
That's Flanders' vigil.
爸爸的在那边
Dad's is over there.
祈祷竟然占据了这份工作这么大的比重
Vigils are a surprisingly large part of this job.
噢耶  好悲伤
Oh, yeah! So sad!
爸爸的好是要慢慢品味的  丽莎
Dad's an acquired taste, Lis,
就像夏威夷比萨一样
like Hawaiian pizza.
爸爸可从来没有因为地域而歧视过披萨
Dad never judged a pizza by where it came from.
他都是先尝了再说
He just ate it.
上帝  现在只有你和我了
God, this is just you and me,
所以我要告诉你一个秘密
so I'm gonna tell you a secret.
我爱我的爸爸  请不要带走他
I love my dad, so please don't take him.
巴仔  你在祈祷什么呢
Bart, what are you praying for?
新单车
New bike.
你真的不想为了你爸爸祈祷吗
Are you sure you don't want to pray for your dad?
我没法祈祷
I can't pray.
没人听得到我的祈祷
I don't think anyone's listening anymore.
亲爱的  祈祷不一定要上帝听到
Oh, sweetie, prayer doesn't have to be to God.
也可以是我们与自己之间的
It can also just be an honest conversation
诚实的对话
we have with ourselves.
听从你的内心
Just do what your heart tells you.
我不知道现在是什么情况
Oh, I'm not really sure what's happening,
但我很难过  我需要帮助
but I'm really sad, and I need help.
亲爱的上帝
救救我爸爸
抄送:耶稣
以防万一也抄送给佛陀
*欢呼吧  雀跃吧*
*Rejoice, rejoice*
*在这春田镇*
*O Springfield town*
*因为在天之灵*
*'Cause what goes up*
*会回到凡间*
*Must come down*
天堂
达夫啤酒
每注投注我都赢了
I'm winning every bet!
而且也没有福克斯的中场广告
And there's no stupid Fox halftime show.
天堂竟然如此美好
Could Heaven be any better?
我同意  这里拥有我梦寐以求的一切
I agree. This is everything I could possibly dream of.
托德在祈祷  在为我祈祷
Todd is praying. He's praying for me.
管用了
And it's working!
我要回到家人身边了
I'm returning to my family!
再见  侯默
Bye, Homer.
-侯默  -妈妈
- Homer? - Mom?
现在我终于能亲口跟你道别了
I never got a chance to say goodbye, but now I can.
记住  我不喜欢拥抱
Remember, I'm not a hugger.
不好意思
Oh, right. Sorry.
你永远不用对我道歉
You never need to apologize to me.
在我眼中你是完美的
In my eyes, you're perfect.
在天堂不用墨守成规
Ah, we're in Heaven.
来抱一个
Come here, you.
我的天啊  我一直在幻想这一刻
Oh, my God, this is all I ever wanted!
可恶
Aw, damn it!
哈利路亚  我又回到了这美丽的世界
Hallelujah! I'm alive and back in this big beautiful world.
我要亲吻见到的第一件东西
I could kiss the first thing I see.
好吧  承诺就是承诺
Ah. Promise is promise.
-老侯  -爸爸
- Homie! - Dad!
-太好了  -太棒了
- Doughboy! - Yay!
爸爸  你回来了  我又相信上帝了
Daddy, you came back! I believe again!
祈祷拯救了两条生命
Two lives saved by prayer.
还有现代药品
And modern medicine.
这就是我成为医生的理由
This is why I became a doctor.
现在你们各欠我12000美金
Because you both owe me $12,000.
不行  不行
No, no, no, no.
涅槃是事成之后的奖励  你又没把事情办妥
Nirvana is for closers, and you couldn't close the deal.
-但是  但  -但什么但
- But-but... - But-but-but-but-but nothing!
你连托德·傅兰德斯都搞不定
You couldn't even close Todd frickin' Flanders!
那孩子看见蝴蝶都会去追
That kid would follow a butterfly.
再给我一次机会
Just give me one more chance.
难道我是靠耐心和容忍才成为佛陀的吗
Do you think I got to be Buddha by being patient?!
看这里  我带来了拉尔夫·韦根
Check this out. I got you Ralph Wiggum.
拉尔夫·韦根  我要拉尔夫·韦根有什么用
Ralph Wiggum? What am I gonna do with Ralph Wiggum?
一切皆成空
Everything is nothing!
孩子  你让我太震惊了
Kid, you just blew my mind.
晚安  罗迪
Good night, Roddy.
*赞美上帝  保佑众生*
*Praise God from whom all blessings flow*
*赞美上帝*
*Praise God*
*又到了该结束的时候*
*It's almost time to go*
*托德已经得偿所愿
*Todd has found just what he seeks*
*下一集两周后播出*
*New episode in two weeks*